Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 639, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: We hold these rights: a guide to women's rights and responsibilities, 1980; Publication (Box 639, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 639, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: How to run a union meeting, 1980; Publication (Box 639, Folder 19)
    Author: AFL- CIO
    Notes: Publication no.81
  - Item 2: How to conduct your union meeting, Publication (Box 639, Folder 19)
    Author: Frank Hanley
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 639, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Union women have just four questions to ask you, Publication (Box 639, Folder 20)
    Author: AFL-CIO; CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women)
  - Item 2: A salaried woman needs a union here's why, Publication (Box 639, Folder 20)
    Author: AFL-CIO. Dept. for Professional Employees
  - Item 3: How to run a union meeting, 1966; Publication (Box 639, Folder 20)
- CIO Department of Education and Research, Publication (Box 639, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Stop runaway shops, 1980; Publication (Box 639, Folder 21)
    Author: Edith L. Perlmutter; Fred Wright
  - Item 2: Rules for union meetings, 1955; Publication (Box 639, Folder 21)
    Author: TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America)
    Notes: Reprinted from a TWUA pamphlet.
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 639, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A union member's guide to employee involvement, 1987; Publication (Box 639, Folder 22)
    Author: Tom Juravich; Howard Harris
  - Item 2: Ready Reference Guide for Local Union Leadership, Publication (Box 639, Folder 22)
    Author: USW (United Steelworkers of America)
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 639, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Labor Party Advocates: Questions and Answers, 1992; Publication (Box 639, Folder 23)
    Author: Labor Party Advocates
  - Item 2: The Great American Sell Out: Fighting Contracting Out, 1988; Publication (Box 639, Folder 23)
    Notes: A Manual for AFSCME Councils and Locals
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 639, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Community action: a local union workbook, 1985; Publication (Box 639, Folder 24)
- CWA (Communication Workers of America), Publication (Box 639, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Unions in our community: CWA our voice, our vote, our future!, Publication (Box 639, Folder 25)
    Author: CWA (Communication Workers of America)
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 639, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Problem solving for local union leadership, Publication (Box 639, Folder 26)
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 639, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Leadership in the local union, Publication (Box 639, Folder 27)
- TDU (Teamsters for a Democratic Union), Publication (Box 639, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Steward's manual, 1986; Publication (Box 639, Folder 28)
    Author: TDU (Teamsters for a Democratic Union)
- International Metalworkers' Federation, Publication (Box 639, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: International comparison of average net hourly earnings, 1981; Publication (Box 639, Folder 29)
    Author: International Metalworkers' Federation
    Notes: Document 81-4
- BLF&E (Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen), Publication (Box 640, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Transportation: Achilles heel of National Security, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 1)
    Author: Andrew F. Schoeppel
    Notes: Speech printed in Congressional Record, 86th Congress, First Session
  - Item 2: The Railroads "Dual" basis of pay, or Railway Management's "Two Days' Pay" Hoax (article), 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 1)
    Author: RLEA (Railway Labor Executives' Association)
    Notes: Railway Labor Fact Sheet no.15, (1959:Sep.)
  - Item 3: 1959 Safety Awards, Publication (Box 640, Folder 1)
    Author: BLF&E (Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen)
  - Item 4: Text and analysis of work rule demands of United States Railroads, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 1)
    Notes: Reprinted from Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, December, 1959
  - Item 5: Representation elections under the Railway Labor Act, 1965; Publication (Box 640, Folder 1)
    Author: Richard B. Peterson
    Notes: Reprint Series no.56. Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, January, 1965
  - Item 6: The Truth about the Railroads: address of G.E. Leighty, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 1)
    Author: G. E. Leighty
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company; New York Central Railroad Company, Publication (Box 640, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Editorials approve the Penn-Central merger, 1963; Publication (Box 640, Folder 2)
    Author: Pennsylvania Railroad Company; New York Central Railroad Company
  - Item 2: Pennsy's merger delayed by court, 1967; Publication (Box 640, Folder 2)
    Author: Fred P. Graham
    Notes: News clipping. Photocopy
  - Item 3: High court blocks Pensy-Central merger till small lines' fate is set, 1967; Publication (Box 640, Folder 2)
    Author: Wall Street Journal
  - Item 4: Seaboard-Coast line merger is cleared by Supreme Court, 1967; Publication (Box 640, Folder 2)
    Author: New York Times
  - Item 5: Supreme Court gives go-ahead on rail merger, 1967; Publication (Box 640, Folder 2)
- BLF&E (Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen), Publication (Box 640, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Rail Review and Report, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1959:Jan.)
  - Item 2: Rail Review and Report, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1959:Feb.)
  - Item 3: Rail Review and Report, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1959:Apr.)
  - Item 4: Rail Review and Report, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1959:June)
  - Item 5: Rail Review and Report, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1959:July/Aug.)
  - Item 6: Rail Review and Report, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1959:Sep.)
  - Item 7: Rail Review and Report, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.9 (1959:Oct.)
  - Item 8: Rail Review and Report, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.11 (1959:Dec.)
- BLF&E (Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen), Publication (Box 640, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Program - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1923; Publication (Box 640, Folder 4)
    Notes: December 2, 1923.
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Tenth Biennial Convention: Report of Proceedings, 1922; Publication (Box 640, Folder 5)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers
    Notes: October 3-5, 1922.
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Eleventh Biennial Convention: Report of Proceedings, 1924; Publication (Box 640, Folder 6)
    Notes: October 7-9, 1924.
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Twelfth Biennial Convention: Report of Proceedings, 1926; Publication (Box 640, Folder 7)
    Notes: October 5-8, 1926.
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Address of President Paul L. Phillips to the twentieth convention, 1952; Publication (Box 640, Folder 8)
    Author: Paul L. Phillips
    Notes: March 24, 1952.
  - Item 2: Wage Conference resolutions: resolutions submitted to the Wage Conference held at the Hollenden Hotel, Cleveland, Ohio..., 1952; Publication (Box 640, Folder 8)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Paper Makers
    Notes: March 24-29, 1952.
- United Paperworkers of America, Publication (Box 640, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Attention: Delegates to the Fourth Constitutional Convention, United Paperworkers of America-CIO, 1955; Publication (Box 640, Folder 9)
    Author: United Paperworkers of America
  - Item 2: Attention: Delegates to the Fourth Constitutional Convention, United Paperworkers of America-CIO, 1955; Publication (Box 640, Folder 9)
    Notes: Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Attention: Delegates to the Fourth Constitutional Convention, United Paperworkers of America-CIO, 1955; Publication (Box 640, Folder 9)
    Notes: Copy 3.
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Standard minimum wage schedule for newsprint mills and other ground wood papers, 1956-1957 (Box 640, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Standard minimum wage schedule for newsprint mills and other ground wood papers, 1956-1957 (Box 640, Folder 10)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Address to Paper Makers Convention, Chicago, March 4, 1957, Publication (Box 640, Folder 11)
    Author: Matthew J. Burns
  - Item 2: Text of a speech delivered today by AFL-CIO Secretary-Treasurer William F. Schnitzler to the merger convention of the United Papermakers and Paperworkers at the Morrison Hotel', 1957; Publication (Box 640, Folder 11)
    Author: William F. Schnitzler
    Notes: Printed in News for the AFL-CIO
  - Item 3: Address by James B. Carey, Secretary-TreasurerThe Betrayal of Trade Unionism, 1957; Publication (Box 640, Folder 11)
    Author: James B. Carey
  - Item 4: Proceedings of the Constitutional Convention, 1957; Publication (Box 640, Folder 11)
    Author: United Papermakers and Paperworkers
  - Item 5: Proceedings of the Constitutional Convention, 1957; Publication (Box 640, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Handwritten prayer for convention, 1957; Publication (Box 640, Folder 11)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Names and addresses of Delegates, Officers and Organizers attending the twenty-first convention at Miami Beach, Florida, Publication (Box 640, Folder 12)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Bio of Jeremiah T. Carey (1870-1957), Publication (Box 640, Folder 13)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Report of Unity Committee, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 14)
    Author: S. A. Stephens; Frank C. Barnes; Godfrey J. Ruddick; Oren Parker
    Notes: March 5, 1959.
  - Item 2: Unity Resolution, 1957; Publication (Box 640, Folder 14)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Twenty-fifth convention, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 15)
    Notes: August 31, 1959.
  - Item 2: Roll call of Delegates to the Twenty-Fifth Convention, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 15)
    Notes: August 31-September 5, 1959.
  - Item 3: Officers and Field Staff (list), Publication (Box 640, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Rules of order governing the Twenty-fifth convention, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Permanent Committees of the Twenty-Fifth Convention of the, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Golden Anniversary materials, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Resolutions presented to the twenty-fifth convention, 1959; Publication (Box 640, Folder 15)
- Newsprint Information Committee, Publication (Box 640, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Newsprint facts, 1962; Publication (Box 640, Folder 16)
    Author: Newsprint Information Committee
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1962:June/July)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: J. Arthur D'Aoust, Second Vice President, Publication (Box 640, Folder 17)
    Author: J. Arthur D'Aoust
    Notes: Biography and Address
    Language: English;French.
  - Item 2: J. Arthur D'Aoust, Second Vice President, Publication (Box 640, Folder 17)
    Notes: Biography and Address. Copy 2.
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Introducing your union, Publication (Box 640, Folder 18)
    Notes: Advance copy.
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The State of the Union -- a report to the membership by Paul L. Phillips, President, International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1951; Publication (Box 640, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Minutes of Joint meeting of the International Executive Boards of the International Brotherhood of Paper, 1957; Publication (Box 640, Folder 19)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Paper Makers; International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers
  - Item 3: Resolution on the achievement of labor unity in the Paper Industry, 1957; Publication (Box 640, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Regional differences - Chapter 10, Part III - the South, Publication (Box 640, Folder 19)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 640, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Times Union, 1949; Publication (Box 640, Folder 20)
    Author: Times Union
    Notes: February 25, 1949.
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Theads, Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Author: The Humanities Project
    Notes: no.1
  - Item 2: Theads, Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.2
  - Item 3: Theads, Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.3
  - Item 4: Theads, Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.4
  - Item 5: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.5 (1979)
  - Item 6: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1979:Apr.)
  - Item 7: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1979:May)
  - Item 8: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1979:June/July)
  - Item 9: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1979:Aug./Sep.)
  - Item 10: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1979:Oct./Nov.)
  - Item 11: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1979:Winter)
  - Item 12: Theads, 1980; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1980:Spring)
  - Item 13: Theads, 1980; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1980:Summer)
  - Item 14: Theads, Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.1. Copy 2.
  - Item 15: Theads, Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.2. Copy 2.
  - Item 16: Theads, Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.3. Copy 2.
  - Item 17: Theads, Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.4. Copy 2.
  - Item 18: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.5 (1979). Copy 2.
  - Item 19: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1979:Apr.). Copy 2.
  - Item 20: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1979:May). Copy 2.
  - Item 21: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1979:June/July). Copy 2.
  - Item 22: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1979:Aug./Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 23: Theads, 1979; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1979:Oct./Nov.). Copy 2.
  - Item 24: Theads, 1980; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1980:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 25: Theads, 1980; Publication (Box 640, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1980:Summer). Copy 2.
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Bank Employees Union, Publication (Box 640, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Oak Park Federal Savings Employees' Voice, Publication (Box 640, Folder 23)
    Author: ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Bank Employees Union
    Notes: v.1:no.2
  - Item 2: Oak Park Federal Savings Employees' Voice, Publication (Box 640, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.1:no.3
  - Item 3: Oak Park Federal Savings Employees' Voice, Publication (Box 640, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.1:no.4
  - Item 4: Oak Park Federal Savings Employees' Voice, Publication (Box 640, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.1:no.5
  - Item 5: Oak Park Federal Savings Employees' Voice, Publication (Box 640, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.1:no.6
  - Item 6: Bank Employees' Voice, Publication (Box 640, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.4:no.4
- Local 1199, Publication (Box 640, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Senior Citizen News, 1972; Publication (Box 640, Folder 24)
    Author: Local 1199
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1972:Summer)
  - Item 2: Senior Citizen News, 1972; Publication (Box 640, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1972:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Senior Citizen News, 1972; Publication (Box 640, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1972:Summer). Copy 3.
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1914-1916, Publication (Box 641, Folder 1)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1916-1918, Publication (Box 641, Folder 2)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Third Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1918-1920, Publication (Box 641, Folder 3)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Fourth Biennial Convention
  - Item 2: Report of the General Executive Board, 1920; Publication (Box 641, Folder 3)
    Notes: Fourth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1920-1922, Publication (Box 641, Folder 4)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Fifth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1922-1924, Publication (Box 641, Folder 5)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Sixth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1924-1926, Publication (Box 641, Folder 6)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Seventh Biennial Convention
  - Item 2: The Seventh Biennial Report of the General Executive Board, 1926; Publication (Box 641, Folder 6)
    Notes: Seventh Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1926-1928, Publication (Box 641, Folder 7)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Eighth Biennial Convention
  - Item 2: The Eighth Biennial Report of the General Executive Board, 1928; Publication (Box 641, Folder 7)
    Notes: Eighth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Ninth Bienneal Convention, 1930; Publication (Box 641, Folder 8)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Ninth Biennial Convention
  - Item 2: The Ninth Biennial Report of the General Executive Board, 1930; Publication (Box 641, Folder 8)
    Notes: Ninth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Tenth Bienneal Convention, 1934; Publication (Box 641, Folder 9)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Tenth Biennial Convention
  - Item 2: The Tenth Biennial Report of the General Executive Board, 1934; Publication (Box 641, Folder 9)
    Notes: Tenth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1934-1936, Publication (Box 641, Folder 10)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Eleventh Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 641, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Documentary History of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1936-1938, Publication (Box 641, Folder 11)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Twelfth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Convention, 1940; Publication (Box 642, Folder 1)
    Notes: Proceedings of the Thirteenth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Fourteenth Biennial Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 642, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: General Executive Board Report, 1944; Publication (Box 642, Folder 2)
    Notes: Fourteenth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Fifteenth Biennial Convention, 1946; Publication (Box 642, Folder 3)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Sixteenth Biennial Convention, 1948; Publication (Box 642, Folder 4)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Seventeenth Biennial Convention, 1950; Publication (Box 642, Folder 5)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Eighteenth Biennial Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 642, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: General Executive Board Report, 1952; Publication (Box 642, Folder 6)
    Notes: Eighteenth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Fortieth Anniversary Convention, 1954; Publication (Box 642, Folder 7)
    Notes: Nineteenth Biennial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Twentieth Biennial Convention, 1956; Publication (Box 642, Folder 8)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Twenty-First Biennial Convention, 1958; Publication (Box 642, Folder 9)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Twenty-Second Biennial Convention, 1960; Publication (Box 642, Folder 10)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Twenty-Third Biennial Convention, 1962; Publication (Box 642, Folder 11)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Fiftieth Anniversary Convention, 1964; Publication (Box 642, Folder 12)
    Notes: Twenty-Fourth Biennial Convention
  - Item 2: General Executive Board Report, 1964; Publication (Box 642, Folder 12)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 642, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report and Proceedings of the Twenty-Fifth Biennial Convention, 1966; Publication (Box 642, Folder 13)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 643, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report, 1966; Publication (Box 643, Folder 1)
    Notes: Twenty-Fifth Biennnial Convention
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 643, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Executive Board Report, 1968; Publication (Box 643, Folder 2)
    Notes: Twenty-Sixth Biennnial Convention
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 643, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Executive Board, 1978; Publication (Box 643, Folder 3)
    Notes: First Constitutional Convention
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 643, Folder 4)